[
    {
      "question": " Artificial Intelligence is about_____",
  
      "option1": " Playing a game on Computer",
  
      "option2": " Making a machine Intelligent",
  
      "option3": " Programming on Machine with your Own Intelligence",
  
      "option4": " Putting your intelligence in Machine",
  
      "answer": " Making a machine Intelligent"
},
    {
        "question": " Who is known as the 'Father of AI'?",
    
        "option1": " Fisher Ada",
    
        "option2": " Alan Turing",
    
        "option3": " John McCarthy",
    
        "option4": " Allen Newell",
    
        "answer": " John McCarthy"
      },
      {
        "question": " Select the most appropriate situation for that a blind search can be used ?",
    
        "option1": " Real-life situation",
    
        "option2": " Small Search Space",
    
        "option3": " Complex game",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " Small Search Space"
      },
      {
        "question": " The application/applications of Artificial Intelligence is/are ",
    
        "option1": " Expert Systems",
    
        "option2": " Gaming",
    
        "option3": " Vision Systems",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": " Among the given options, which search algorithm requires less memory ?",
    
        "option1": " Optimal Search",
    
        "option2": " Depth First Search",
    
        "option3": " Breadth-First Search",
    
        "option4": " Linear Search",
    
        "answer": " Depth First Search"
      },
      {
        "question": "  If a robot is able to change its own trajectory as per the external conditions, then the robot is considered as the__",
    
        "option1": " Mobile",
    
        "option2": " Non-Servo",
    
        "option3": " Open Loop",
    
        "option4": " Intelligent",
    
        "answer": " Intelligent"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI ?",
    
        "option1": " LISP",
    
        "option2": " PROLOG",
    
        "option3": " Python",
    
        "option4": " Perl",
    
        "answer": " Perl"
      },
      {
        "question": " A technique that was developed to determine whether a machine could or could not demonstrate the artificial intelligence known as the___",
    
        "option1": " Boolean Algebra",
    
        "option2": " Turing Test",
    
        "option3": " Logarithm",
    
        "option4": " Algorithm",
    
        "answer": " Turing Test"
      },
      {
        "question": " The component of an Expert system is_________.",
    
        "option1": " Knowledge Base",
    
        "option2": " Inference Engine",
    
        "option3": " User Interface",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which algorithm is used in the Game tree to make decisions of Win/Lose ?",
    
        "option1": " Heuristic Search Algorithm",
    
        "option2": " DFS/BFS algorithm",
    
        "option3": " Greedy Search Algorithm",
    
        "option4": " Min/Max algorithm",
    
        "answer": " Min/Max algorithm"
      }
    
    
    
]